<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<knimeNode
	icon="./salesforce.png"
	type="Manipulator" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v4.1"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v4.1 http://knime.org/node/v4.1.xsd">
	<name>Salesforce Simple Query</name>
	<shortDescription>Read fields from a Salesforce object</shortDescription>
	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			<p>
				Read fields from a Salesforce object. In the configuration dialog select the object type 
				(i.e. a table in Salesforce such <i>Account</i>) and the corresponding object fields 
				(columns, such as <i>Account Name</i>); the data is returned in a KNIME table at the output. 
				An optional <i>WHERE</i> and <i>LIMIT</i> statement can be specified to narrow the search result.
			</p>
		</intro>
		<option name="Names based on">
			Determines whether the column names in the output table are derived from the Salesforce 
			field <i>names</i> or <i>labels</i>. Labels are human readable and also used in the Salesforce user
			interface, e.g. <i>AI Record Insight ID</i>. Field names are names used in the API, e.g. <i>AiRecordInsightId</i>.
			Most standard fields use the same name as the label. Custom fields will have the '_ _c' suffix. The option
			also controls how fields and objects are displayed in the configuration dialog.     
		</option>
		<option name="Salesforce Object">
			The objects as available in Salesforce. The list is queried when the dialog is opened. The list only 
			contains objects, which are <i>queryable</i> (a property set in Salesforce). 
		</option>
		<option name="Selected Fields">
			The fields defined for the selected object. Move the fields that should be retrieved into the 'Include' 
			list. The field's type is mapped to a native KNIME type (string, int, double, boolean, 
			date &amp; time, ...), whereby some types may not be supported (for instance Salesforce's <i>anyType</i>). 
			Fields with such unsupported type are hidden in the configuration dialog.
		</option>
		<option name="WHERE clause">
			An optional WHERE clause to filter the result set. Examples are 
			<pre>
Name LIKE 'A%' 
CreatedDate > 2011-04-26T10:00:00-08:00
CALENDAR_YEAR(CreatedDate) = 2011</pre>
			(find some examples in the Salesforce 
			<a href="https://developer.salesforce.com/docs/atlas.en-us.soql_sosl.meta/soql_sosl/sforce_api_calls_soql_select_conditionexpression.htm">
			online documentation)</a>.  
		</option>
		<option name="LIMIT result set">
			An optional integer to constraint the result set to a maximum number as specified.
		</option>
		<option name="Also retrieve deleted and archived records">
			When selected, the node will use Salesforce’s <a href="https://developer.salesforce.com/docs/atlas.en-us.api_rest.meta/api_rest/resources_queryall.htm">
			queryAll</a> endpoint to include deleted and archived records in the results.
		</option>
	</fullDescription>
	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Authentication">
			Salesforce Authentication Object
		</inPort>
		<outPort index="0" name="Salesforce Result Table">
			A table containing the selected fields. Column names are derived from the field labels.
		</outPort>
	</ports>
</knimeNode>