<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./salesforce_connect.png" type="Source"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v4.1"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v4.1 http://knime.org/node/v4.1.xsd">
	<name>Salesforce Authentication</name>
	<shortDescription>Authenticate with Salesforce</shortDescription>
	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
		<p>
			Authenticate with Salesforce. Authentication currently only succeeds with KNIME's test instance on 
			https://test.salesforce.com
		</p>
		<p></p>
	    <p>
			<b>Important:</b>
			When choosing the <i>Node</i> credentials storage location,
			the node saves a refresh token with access to your Microsoft account
			(with the specified permissions) in the node settings. Before sharing
			the workflow, you should clear your credentials in the node dialog.
	    </p>
			<p />
		</intro>
		<tab name="Authenticaion">
			<option name="Authenticate">
				Press this button to authentication with Salesforce.
				A page will be opened in your browser, which will ask you to sign in
				to your Salesforce account. Once you are logged in, you will be asked
				to accept the permission requests of the KNIME Analytics Platform
				application if you did not accept the permissions previously. If the
				authentication succeeded, you will be redirected to a page that
				states that the verification code has been received and that you may
				close the window. The status in the node dialog will update to
				"Authenticated".
			</option>
			<option name="Cancel">
				Cancel a running authentication process.
			</option>
			<option name="Credentials Storage Location">
				Select where authentication credentials should be stored:
				<ul>
				<li>
					<b>Memory</b>
					: The authentication credentials will be kept in memory. 
					They are discarded when closing KNIME. 
				</li>
				<li>
					<b>Local File</b>
					: The authentication credentials will be saved and loaded to and from the selected
					file. 
				</li>
				<li>
					<b>Node</b>
					: The authentication credentials will be saved in the node settings. If you choose this
					option, the workflow will contain your authentication information after is has been saved. 
					Thus, access to your Microsoft account will be available to others if you share the workflow. 
				</li>
			</ul>
			</option>
			<option name="Clear Selected Credentials">
				Deletes the authentication credentials stored at the selected location.
				If <i>Local File</i> was selected, the file will be deleted if
				it contains previously stored credentials. Otherwise, the file will be left
				untouched and an error is displayed. If <i>Node</i> was selected, the credentials will
				be cleared from the node settings <b>not before</b> saving the workflow.
			</option>
			<option name="Clear All Credentials">
				Deletes all stored authentication credentials. Also see description of 
				<i>Clear Selected Credentials</i> button. In case you do not want to share your credentials
				with this workflow, all credentials should be cleared beforehand. 
			</option>
		</tab>
	</fullDescription>
	<ports>
		<outPort index="0" name="Salesforce Authentication">The authentication including the tokens to access remote resources.</outPort>
 </ports>
</knimeNode>