<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./salesforce.png" type="Source"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v4.1"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v4.1 http://knime.org/node/v4.1.xsd"
	deprecated="true">
	<name>Salesforce Authentication</name>
	<shortDescription>Authenticate with Salesforce</shortDescription>
	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
		<p>
			Authenticate with Salesforce. The authentication information can be used to query Salesforce 
			using the <i>Salesforce SOQL</i> node or to extract temporary access tokens used in nodes 
			such as <i>GET Request</i>.  Note that in order to use this node the KNIME Analytics Platform 
			needs to be registered with the respective Salesforce domain. Please contact your Salesforce 
			administrator or <a href="https://www.knime.com/contact">KNIME</a> to get more information. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Two types of authentication are supported, <i>OAuth2 Interactive Authentication</i> and
			<i>Username &amp; Password</i> authentication. If in doubt, use the former as username
			&amp; password authentication is discouraged according to the Salesforce documentation.  
		</p>
		</intro>
		<tab name="OAuth2 Interactive Authentication">
			<option name="Authenticate">
				<p>
					Press this button to authentication with Salesforce.
					A page will be opened in your browser, which will ask you to sign in
					to your Salesforce account. Once you are logged in, you will be asked
					to accept the permission requests of the KNIME Analytics Platform
					application if you did not accept the permissions previously. If the
					authentication succeeded, you will be redirected to a page that
					states that the verification code has been received and that you may
					close the window. The status in the node dialog will update to
					"Authenticated". 
				</p>
				<p>
					When choosing the Node credentials storage location, the node saves a
					refresh token with access to your Salesforce account (with the specified
					permissions) in the node settings. Before sharing the workflow, you
					should clear your credentials in the node dialog.
				</p>
			</option>
			<option name="Credentials Storage Location">
				Select where authentication credentials should be stored:
				<ul>
				<li>
					<b>Memory</b>: The authentication credentials will be kept in memory. 
					They are discarded when closing KNIME. 
				</li>
				<li>
					<b>Local File</b>: The authentication credentials will be saved and 
					loaded to and from the selected file. 
				</li>
				<li>
					<b>Node</b>:
					The authentication credentials will be saved in the node settings. If you choose this
					option, the workflow will contain your authentication information after is has been saved. 
					Thus, access to your Microsoft account will be available to others if you share the workflow. 
				</li>
				</ul>
			</option>
			<option name="Clear Selected Credentials">
				Deletes the authentication credentials stored at the selected location.
				If <i>Local File</i> was selected, the file will be deleted if
				it contains previously stored credentials. Otherwise, the file will be left
				untouched and an error is displayed. If <i>Node</i> was selected, the credentials will
				be cleared from the node settings <b>not before</b> saving the workflow.
			</option>
			<option name="Clear All Credentials">
				Deletes all stored authentication credentials. Also see description of 
				<i>Clear Selected Credentials</i> button. In case you do not want to share your credentials
				with this workflow, all credentials should be cleared beforehand. 
			</option>
		</tab>
		<tab name="Username + Password Authentication">
			<option name="Credentials">
				<p>
					Choose a credentials object to control username and password (generally
					preferred, especially when used on KNIME Server)
				</p>
			</option>
			<option name="Username &amp; password">
				<p>
					Enter username, password and security token directly. Note the password
					and security token will be saved as part of the node configuration in a
					weakly encrypted (symmetric) format. The <i>Security Token</i> can be
					reset in the users's Salesforce Account settings.
				</p>
			</option>
		</tab>
		<tab name="Instance Type">
			<option name="Use Production Instance">
				<p>
					Uses the production org. If in doubt, use this.  
				</p>
			</option>
			<option name="Use Test Instance">
				<p>
					Connects to a Salesforce sandbox instance, which is isolated from the production org.
				</p>
			</option>
		</tab>
		<tab name="Connection Settings">
			<option name="Connection timeout (seconds)">
				<p>
					The http connection timeout used in this node and also downstream nodes when connecting to the salesforce instance.  
				</p>
			</option>
			<option name="Read timeout (seconds)">
				<p>
					The http read timeout used in this node and also downstream nodes when connecting to the salesforce instance.  
				</p>
			</option>
		</tab>
	</fullDescription>
	<ports>
		<outPort index="0" name="Credential">
			The authentication including the tokens to access remote resources.
			Note the token itself is not saved as part of the port content.
			Especially when choosing the keep the authentication information "In
			Memory" (see above) it will be invalid when closing and re-opening the
			workflow (downstream nodes will fail albeit the node itself shown as
			executed).
		</outPort>
 </ports>
</knimeNode>